LUCIJA JAKŠIĆ

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



+385 99 85 97 165



lucia.jaksic@gmail.com



Zagreb, Croatia, European Union

About Me

With over 6 years of expertise in full stack web development, I'm an experienced software professional eager to transition to mobile development. My background in creating user-friendly web applications, coupled with a proficiency in programming languages and frameworks, equips me for this shift. I have build a number of mobile applications during my masters (some of them still being actively used) and have spent last year learning iOS development and building my own mobile application that is published on App Store.

Experience

Self-employed (May 2023 - today)

iOS engineer

I am working on an iOS application <u>Frequency: Sound Generator</u>. (Swift, SwiftUI, XCode, iOS, App Store, Concurrency, Mobile Application Development)

Huddle (Jul 2022 - Jan 2024)

Full Stack Engineer

I was working as a full stack .NET engineer on a solution that provided automated pricing for gaming operators. (C#, ASP.NET, MS SQL Server, React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git, Jira, Confluence, Jenkins, Portainer)

Ekobit (Apr 2022 - Jul 2022)

Full Stack Engineer

I was working as a full stack .NET/React engineer on the development of administrative interface for smart building management application: managing user administration and integration of other modules. (C#, ASP.NET, MS SQL Server, React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git)

Lemax (Aug 2019 - Mar 2022)

Full Stack Engineer

I was working as a full stack .NET engineer within an agile team that developed SaaS platform for DMCs & tour operators. Responsible for code quality through following SOLID principles and design patterns. Ensuring the quality of the developed functionalities covering them with unit and integration tests. (C#, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Web Forms, MS SQL Server, Entity Framework, xUnit, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Team Foundation Server (TFS), Jira, Confluence, Jenkins, Kibana, SonarQube, SonarLint, Postman)

Instantor (Oct 2017 - Jun 2019)

Backend Engineer / Student Team Lead

I was working as a Java backend engineer on the implementation of Instantor services for financial institutions throughout Europe. I also served as a team lead, overseeing a group of talented engineering students that worked on a scraping tool based in Java. (Java, Git, HTML, CSS)

Education

Master's Degree in Computer Science (Oct 2014 - Jul 2019)

University of Zagreb, Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing

- -> Co-author of ConTEL research paper: "Virtual Reality Serious Game Prototype for Presenting Military Units" C#, Unity
- -> Implemeted "Mobile application for automated voice notification" Automated voice notification for people with visual impairments (Android application)
- -> Implemented "ICT-ACC Jezicno-govorna vjezbalica" Cross platform and mobile application for communication and language skill support (Android, iOS and desktop application)

Skills

Languages

Swift, SwiftUI, XCode, App Store, iOS, Concurrency, Mobile Application Development, Object Oriented Programming, .NET, C#, SQL Server, Design Patterns, Unit Testing, Integration Testing, .NET Core, Microservices, Git, CSS, HTML, Jenkins

Croatian (1st language) English (C1) German (B2) - DSD II